http://www.bonefishgrill.com/privacy-rights/privacy-policy

Go
Please enter a zip code or both city and state.
Use current location
We're sorry, there are no Bonefish Grill locations within
of .
Showing results within of .
Reservations
,
Find a different location
Call for parties larger than 6.
The time selected is not available. Please select from our available times.
Valid Phone Number required
A text will be sent to you when your table is ready. Message and Data Rates May Apply.
Based on your email address, it looks like you’re from a region that is outside of our marketable area.
Valid Email required
Yes, I acknowledge that I am 18 years of age or older.
Please sign me up to be a BFG Insider and be the first to get regular updates on all things Bonefish Grill.
Please Note: This is not a reservation. You have been added to the current wait list. You may have a short wait once you arrive at the restaurant.
Est. Arrival Time:
Where:
When:
# of Guest:
Phone #:
Email Address:
Special Occasion:
Modify
Confirm
Plan to arrive By:
Where:
When:
Who:
# of Guest:
Email Address:
Please Note: This is not a reservation. You have been added to the current wait list. You may have a short wait once you arrive at the restaurant.
Tonight's specials
Get directions
Are you sure you wish to cancel this reservation? Clicking YES will cancel this reservation.
Go
Please enter a zip code or both city and state.
Use current location
See all Locations
We're sorry, there are no Bonefish Grill locations within
of .
Showing results within of .
Your closest Bonefish Grill
,
,
Opens in new window
Privacy Policy California Privacy Notice Accessibility Statement Dine Rewards Terms & Conditions Terms & Conditions
This Privacy Policy applies to information about you that Bloomin’ Brands, Inc.
(“BBI”, “we”,
“our”, “us”) may obtain
when you visit our websites including bloominbrands.com, outback.com,
carrabbas.com,
bonefishgrill.com,
flemingssteakhouse.com, aussiegrill.com, outbackandcarrabbasexpress.com or dine-rewards.com (collectively, the
“Sites”); use
any of the associated
mobile applications (the “Apps”); or connect to the WiFi in our locations (the
Sites, Apps, and
WiFi are
collectively referred to as the “Services” in this Policy). This Privacy Policy
describes how we
may collect, use,
or share information about you; your choices regarding our use of your information; how we
safeguard such
information; and how you may contact us regarding our privacy practices.
Collection
of
personal information Information you provide. We may obtain information that you provide directly to us through the Services when, for example,
you create an account, submit an order, look up nearby restaurants, make a reservation,
download one of our apps, sign up
for special offers, fill out a contact form, submit an order for a gift card, apply for a job,
log in to a WiFi network in one of our restaurants, or otherwise interact with the Services. The
information we obtain may include personal information, which is information that can be used to
identify you individually, such as your name, address, email address, phone number, date of
birth, company affiliation, payment information, or geolocation. Information collected automatically. We also may collect certain information about you automatically using various tools and
technologies such as cookies and web server logs whenever you interact with the Services.
Information collected in this manner may include IP addresses, device identifiers,
device model, device carrier information, software version, browser
characteristics, operating system details, language preferences, referring URLs, length of
visits, MAC address and pages viewed. A cookie is a piece of data that a website can send to your browser, which may then be stored on
your hard drive as an anonymous tag that identifies your computer. Many web browsers are set to
accept cookies by default, but you may be able to set your browser to notify you before you
receive a cookie or to remove or reject cookies. Please note that if you disable cookies, you
may not be able to use certain features of the Sites or other websites, and disabling cookies
may invalidate opt-outs that rely on cookies to function.
We may combine certain automatically-collected information with other information we obtain about
you, which may include data we obtain from third parties. Please note that we or third parties may collect personal information about your online
activities over time and across different devices and online properties when you use the
Services.
Your web browser may have settings that allow you to transmit a “Do Not Track” signal
when you
visit various websites or use online services. Like many websites, the Sites are not designed to
respond to “Do Not Track” signals received from browsers. To learn more about
“Do Not Track”
signals, visit www.allaboutdnt.com. Information collected through the Apps. Depending on your personal device and App permission settings, when using the Apps, we may
collect or have access to the following types of information:
• Precise geolocation. When enabled, this may allow the Apps to
collect real-time
information about the location of your device (GPS and network-based) to provide requested
location services and to serve you relevant offers or promotions. • Stored information and files. These may allow the Apps to read,
modify, or delete
the contents of your USB storage including photographs, audio and video clips, personal
contacts, and address book information.
• Camera. This may allow the Apps to access the camera to scan and
input payment
method details.
• WiFi connection information. When enabled, this may allow the Apps
to view WiFi
connections.
• Other. The Apps will send and receive data to and from the Internet,
and may view
network connections, have full network access, control vibration of your device, or prevent
your device from sleeping.
We will store personal information we obtain through the Apps for no longer than is necessary to
achieve the purposes for which the information was collected, or as otherwise required or
permitted under applicable law.
With respect to information we collect via Apple services (e.g., iOS), we will obtain your
consent before sharing your personal information with third parties for those third
parties’
direct marketing purposes. Information obtained from other parties. Our service providers may provide us with personal information that you submit to them. For
example, if you apply for a job using the career portal, purchase a gift card, order catering,
provide feedback on a recent visit, make a reservation, place an order with a delivery service,
or log in to our restaurant WiFi networks using your social media account, you may submit
personal information to one or more of our service providers that may share your information
with us. We may combine information that we have about you with information we obtain from other
parties. When you submit information to another party, you are subject to that third
party’s
terms of use and privacy policies, for which we are not responsible. Use of Personal Information We may use personal information we collect through the Services for:
• Facilitating and personalizing your user experience;
• Responding to your requests, inquiries, or job applications;
• Processing your transactions;
• Communicating or marketing to you;
• Conducting contests and processing prizes;
• Monitoring and analyzing trends, usage, and activities of users of the Services;
• Improving the Services (e.g. bug fixes and repairing app crashes);
• Complying with applicable laws, regulations, or legal process as well as industry
standards and our company policies;
• Preventing, investigating, identifying, or taking any other action with regard to any
suspected or actual fraudulent or illegal activity, or activity that violates our policies;
or
• Any other purpose, with your consent.
We or our service providers may create de-identified information records from your personal
information
by excluding certain information that makes the information personally identifiable to you. This
de-identified
information may be used to analyze request patterns or usage patterns to enhance our or our
service providers'
products and services.
Sharing of Personal Information We may share your personal information with our subsidiaries, business partners, and vendors that
provide services on our behalf. These parties are not meant to use personal information except
for the purpose(s) for which it was provided.
In the event of a business transaction, such as if we sell or transfer all or a portion of our
business or assets (e.g., further to a merger, reorganization, liquidation, or any other
business transaction, including negotiations of such transactions), we reserve the right to
disclose any information we obtain through the Services. You acknowledge that such transfers may
occur and are permitted by and subject to this Privacy Policy.
Additionally, BBI may disclose personal information when required by subpoena, search warrant, or
other legal processes, or in response to activities that are unlawful or a violation of
BBI’s
rules for use of the Services, or to protect and defend the rights or property of BBI.
Analytics and Advertising We may use third-party technology to collect and use data in connection with interest-based
advertising. These ad technology companies and advertisers may use, store, or access cookies,
web beacons, and other storage technologies to collect or receive information from the Services
and elsewhere on the Internet and use that information to provide advertising services to us,
including interest-based advertising or advertisements targeted to your interests delivered over
time and across online services and devices.
We may use certain web analytics services, for example, Google Analytics, to help us understand
and analyze how visitors use the Services and to serve ads on our behalf across the Internet.
We’ve implemented Google Analytics Advertising Features such as remarketing with
analytics,
interest-based advertising, demographics and interests reporting, user segment analysis,
and impression reporting. We and third-party vendors may use first-party cookies or other
first-party identifiers as well as third-party cookies or other third-party identifiers to
deliver advertisements, create a profile of you, measure your interests, detect your
demographics, detect your location, personalize content, or create an account for management of
our customer loyalty program.
To find out more about how these analytics services manage the privacy of information in
conjunction with delivering ads online and how to opt-out of information collection by these
networks, visit www.youradchoices.com and www.networkadvertising.org. For more information on how Google Analytics uses data collected through the Services, visit
www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners. To opt out of Google Analytics
cookies, visit
adssettings.google.com and tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout. Please note that we do not control how other parties manage their opt-out processes.
Social Networks Certain features of the Services may permit you to initiate interactions between the Services and
other parties, such as social networks (for example, to log in to a restaurant’s WiFi
network or
invite friends to join Dine Rewards). Using these features may allow both BBI and the other
service to access certain information about your use of our Services and theirs, including
personal information. You should review the terms, policies, and settings of those third-party
services to learn more about their data practices and/or adjust your settings.
Sweepstakes, Contests, and Other Promotions
We may operate sweepstakes, contests, raffles, and similar promotions (each, a
“Promotion”)
jointly sponsored or offered by other parties; participating in these Promotions may require you
to submit certain personal information. If you choose to participate in a Promotion, your
personal information may be disclosed to other parties as described in the terms applicable to
that Promotion. Insofar as the terms applicable to a particular Promotion conflict with this
Privacy Policy, the terms applicable to the Promotion shall control.
Linked Websites The Services may include links to other websites that are not owned or operated by BBI. This
Privacy Policy does not apply to those websites, which may have their own privacy policies or
notices that you should review to understand how they may collect, use, or disclose your
personal information. BBI is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of any linked
websites that are operated by third parties.
The Services also may provide links to other websites operated by BBI or our subsidiaries. Unless
indicated otherwise, these websites are not governed by this Privacy Policy. For information on
how these websites may collect, use, or disclose your personal information, we encourage you to
review the privacy policies posted on the linked websites.
Security
We take reasonable measures to protect personal information from loss, theft, misuse,
unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction. Nevertheless, transmission via the
Internet and digital storage are not completely secure and we cannot guarantee the security of
your information collected through the Services.
Your Choices
Communication preferences and marketing. If you do not wish to receive marketing emails from us, you can opt out of future marketing
emails by following the instructions provided in the marketing emails. Opting out of marketing
emails will not affect our administrative or transactional emails to you (e.g., emails about
your transactions or
policy changes) which we may send you, for example, to notify you of an issue with an order you
have placed with us. If you provide your phone number through the Services, we or our third party vendor may call or
send you a transactional
SMS message about the status of or issues with a recent transaction (e.g., an order you have
placed with us).
In addition to transactional SMS messages, we may send you marketing communications by SMS.
However, we only send marketing SMS messages to those who have expressly opted-in to receiving
marketing communications by
SMS text message. If you no longer wish to receive SMS text messages from us, you can opt out of
future
text messages by replying to one of our SMS text messages with the word “Stop.”
Additionally, you may request to stop receiving marketing communications by contacting us at privacy@bloominbrands.com.
Accessing, changing, and deleting your personal information.
If you are a registered user of the Services, you may review and change certain personal
information (e.g., email, password, phone number, payment information) at any time by accessing
your account online.
Location tracking. You may be able to enable or disable location tracking through the Apps by adjusting the
permissions in your account or device settings. Be aware that if GPS precise location services
are disabled, other means of establishing or estimating location (e.g., connecting to or
proximity to WiFi, Bluetooth, beacons, or our networks) may persist. Enabling location tracking
may enable an App to track your location in the background, which may decrease battery life. App permissions.
You may be able to enable or disable certain features (e.g., allowing the Apps to read, modify,
or delete the contents of your USB storage; take pictures and videos; view WiFi connection) by
adjusting the permissions in your device settings. Uninstallation. If you want to terminate our ability to obtain information from you through the Apps, you may
uninstall the Apps from your device.
California Residents California residents may click here to
view our California Privacy Notice.
Nevada Residents Nevada residents may click here to exercise their privacy rights.
Information for Users Outside the United States
If you are visiting the Sites or using the Apps from outside the United States, please be aware
that information we obtain about you will be processed in the United States or in other
jurisdictions. By using the Services, you acknowledge your personal information may be
transferred to and processed in jurisdictions outside your own as described in this Privacy
Policy. Please be aware that the data protection laws and regulations that apply to your
personal information transferred to the United States or other countries may be different from
the laws in your country of residence.
Revisions
This Privacy Policy is subject to change at our discretion. We will indicate changes, including
material changes, to the Privacy Policy by updating the “Effective Date” at the top
of this
page. Your continued use of the Services after any update to this Privacy Policy will constitute
your acceptance of the changes.
Contact Information
You may direct comments or questions regarding this Privacy Policy via email to privacy@bloominbrands.com
